http://www.yumasun.com/site/privacy.html

Home
The Yuma Sun considers your privacy important. We are committed to protecting the privacy of all those who provide us with their contact information while using our information, products, events, or services. This policy describes the ways that personally identifiable and anonymous information about our publication subscribers, online media product users, and event registrants is collected, how that information might be shared, and how someone can request changes to the way their personal information is used or shared.This Privacy Policy applies to websites operated by or on behalf of The Yuma Sun, its subsidiaries, affiliates, divisions and related companies. This Privacy Policy applies only to personal information collected by The Yuma Sun. Be aware that our websites may contain links to other websites that are maintained by third parties who are not required to comply with this Privacy Policy and for which The Yuma Sun has no responsibility. Please review the privacy policies on any external websites to determine their information handling practices.Personally identifiable information is information that can identify you, such as your full name, email address, postal address, and telephone number.We collect personally identifiable information that you choose to provide to us when you subscribe to our newspapers, sign up for email newsletters, enter a contest; participate in surveys, register for a web site, webcast; or otherwise communicate with us. When you provide this information to us, you are no longer anonymous.We also may receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information you have provided to us.If you purchase products or services on our website or through one of our printed forms, you may choose to provide us with your credit card information.The Yuma Sun is not responsible for the information you volunteer about yourself in discussions in our forums or in publicly accessible interactions, or the information that you choose to make public in your member profile. To view or change your member profile, please return to the site where you registered.ANONYMOUS INFORMATION WE COLLECTWe use cookies and other Internet technologies to enrich your online experience by managing our website and email programs. Our cookies do not contain any information, in itself, that is personally identifiable.If your browser is set to allow cookies, we may store small amounts of information on your computer about what parts of our websites you have visited and what features you like best. We may then tailor the content you see to match your interests. We also may use cookies to identify members so that they don't have to re-enter their usernames and passwords. Cookies may also be used to limit the number of advertisements you see while on our site. By allowing us to understand how you use our site over time, cookies can help us provide you with a better, more relevant online experience. The cookies we store on your computer are not accessible on any other companies' websites. Some ads on our site are provided by outside companies. If these ads contain cookies, they can be accessed only by those advertisers; we do not have access to them.Most browsers allow you to modify your security to accept or reject cookies. You need not have cookies turned on to visit our sites, but without them, your access to some areas may be limited and custom navigation may not be available to you.Like many websites, The Yuma Sun may use pixel tags. Pixel tags help us improve our understanding of our web traffic and visitor behavior, as well as gauge the response to our promotional efforts. This information is non-personally identifiable and is used for an aggregate picture of how visitors use our site.We may use industry-standard, third party advertising service companies to serve advertisements when you visit our sites or open our emails. These companies may use cookies, pixel tags, and other methods to collect information (typically not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our website and other web sites to provide you with relevant advertisements about products, services, and events tailored to your interests. You may opt out of receiving targeted advertising from several advertising networks by visiting a website operated by the National Advertising Initiative.  Go to http://optout.networkadvertising.org to opt out of several third-party advertiser networks by using a tool created by the Network Advertising InitiativeWe may use your contact information for any of the following reasons:To provide you with information about products or services you've ordered, or show interest in;We may also use your contact information to ask for your input to help in our research about our services, events, or products or to provide you with additional information about this site and about other The Yuma Sun products, services, or events that we think might be of interest to you.All promotional and research email messages you receive from us will include an option to opt out of future email communications from that particular Yuma Sun business.We may also send you e-newsletters with targeted, relevant content. Each e-newsletter will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of that particular e-newsletter.In some cases, we may send you relevant, carefully-screened offers from reputable third-party businesses or organizations. Many of our customers appreciate receiving these offers because they relate to their business or occupation. However, you will always be able to opt out of receiving future third party offers.We may provide contact lists to third party companies that we have employed to provide us with specialized services, including customer service, subscription fulfillment, research, statistical analysis, list cleansing, postal mailings, email deployment, telemarketing, and other information services. In compliance with privacy laws, we also provide our opt-out lists to those third-party companies so that they can be suppressed from the communications those companies send on The Yuma Sun’s behalf. We only deal with third party companies whom we believe share our commitment to privacy and who will keep your information secure.If you provide information on a co-branded site or while using a co-branded service, you grant us permission to share the information you have provided with that service or site partner. Their use of your information is subject to their privacy policies.Certain information, such as your password and credit card information, is never disclosed in any form whatsoever to any outside party.In the case of a change of ownership or a merger involving The Yuma Sun or any business that is part of The Yuma Sun, your contact information associated with that business would be one of those transferred assets.We use reasonable precautions, including appropriate technical, administrative, and physical procedures, to protect personal information from loss, misuse, or alteration.When we contract with other companies to provide us with services, we only share personal information with those that we believe share our commitment to privacy and information security. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of these parties.Due to the design of the Internet and other factors outside our control, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and our servers will be free from unauthorized access by third parties.By using any of our websites, you consent to our use of your contact information as it is outlined in this privacy statement.The Yuma Sun reserves the right to access and disclose personally identifiable information to comply with applicable laws, lawful government requests and court orders, or to investigate alleged fraud or violations of the Terms of Use of The Yuma Sun website.If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post the changes on this page. Users are encouraged to review this page for any changes. Your continued use of this site constitutes your acceptance of this entire privacy statement.If you wish to contact The Yuma Sun about its privacy policy, please send your specific questions to: admin@yumasun.com.
Right Now
55°
Clear
Humidity: 71%
Cloud Coverage:%
Wind:
3 mph
UV Index: 0 Low
Sunrise: 07:30:05 AM
Sunset: 05:32:40 PM
Today
Clear skies. Low 46F. Winds light and variable.
Tonight
Clear skies. Low 46F. Winds light and variable.
Tomorrow
Sunshine and clouds mixed. High 69F. Winds ESE at 5 to 10 mph.
Latest News
Official concerned with strain on local healthcare system
More than half of inmates in ASPC-Yuma La Paz unit test positive for COVID-19
Yuma Sector Border Patrol asks the public to report any suspicious drone activity
Judge tosses suit seeking to decertify Biden win in Arizona
Crane board meeting at a glance
US-Pres-Sum,100
In Arizona, Trump's false claims have torn open a GOP rift
YC powered by youth, lean on senior experience
Most Popular
Articles
Images
Videos
Commented
ArticlesYuma County's Most Wantedhearing for San Luis man charged with molesting 13-year-old girl continued until next yearIn CustodyDrugs seized at home after domestic disturbanceContinuance granted in fatal shooting caseComings and Goings: LemonGrass now serving up Asian cuisinenew charges filed against man charged in fatal motel shootingMan gets prison sentence in child molestation caseYuma County's Most WantedCounty marks COVID record: 735 new cases
Images
VideosSorry, there are no recent results for popular videos.
CommentedSorry, there are no recent results for popular commented articles.
Submit an ObituaryFamily members may submit obituaries of their loved ones here.
Click Here
© Copyright 2020 Yumasun.com, 2055 Arizona Avenue Yuma, AZ | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
